[Music]
have you got color
do you ever get that feel that you got
the type that sticks around like
commenting you see amazes up your sleep
but you no idea that you're indeed
I dreamt about you nearly every night
this week many secrets can you keep the
bestest June I found my makes me think
I've you somehow when I play it I'll
repeat until I fall asleep spilling
drinks on my sexy
[Music]
shut up
you stay
[Music]
the same thing
you can't say tomorrow day crawling at
you
[Applause]
back to you so have you got the good
been wondering if your heart still open
and if so I wanna know what time it sure
simmer down
Pokhara I'm sorry to interrupt it's just
I'm constantly I miss you
I don't know
the same as I do
we did lead to
[Music]
if you wanted to
we start out in that you'd stay
laughs
[Music]
tomorrow
whoa
[Music]
you